share-ex.com 2015-05-23

# Get Free | Facebook Likes | Twitter Followers | YouTube Views

## Privacy

We respect your privacy and are obliged to protect your online security by keeping your privacy anytime you visit Share-ex.  
Our Privacy Policy and Terms of Use provide complete explanation regarding your personal data provided to us.  
Our Privacy Policy is updated periodically, so you should visit here regularly.  

Gathered Information

During different operations of our website information can be collected by means of the following actions:  
Information regarding your visit(s) to website and use of resources is collected. The information is collected, including location data, weblogs, traffic data, and any other communication information.  
Information provided in any forms filled out on Share-ex is recorded such as registration and purchase information.  
If for any reason you contact our administration, support or website, we can collect information.  
We will never store CC/DC data. 

Use of cookies

We can use cookies to collect information regarding our services to provide analytical data for our website and our advertisers.  
You no personal details will be shared with anyone, which allows identifying you. The information collected by us is just statistical data about visitors and how they have used our site.  
We can use a cookie file to collect information about your common internet use. The cookies will be automatically downloaded to your computer and saved on the hard drive. The collected data by the cookie helps us improve our website and services. You can decline cookies anytime by setting your browser options. But, if you decline the download of cookies, some features of our site may not work. 

The Use of Your Information

Your Information helps us improve and offer services according to your need. You can see how we may use data in the list below:  
You information can be used while making any canges or Improvements to the. You will be notified of such changes.  
We can use at our own or let third parties use information. This can be done only with your permission.  
If you don't want to give permission for our site or third party you can decline. If you decline we will remove your details from any third party communications or mailings immediately.  
Your Information will be stored on secure servers. Transaction data is encrypted for your safety.  
Note : Information provided via online transmission is not entirely secure. We cannot guarantee total protection and security data; we are only responsible to protect information sent to us electronically. Transmission of any data by is at your own risk. The responsibility for the passwords safety and confidentiality is your own.  

Information Exposer

At times we can reveal your personal information to people in our group. This can include subsidiaries, holding companies or any others.  
Third Party disclosure may happen for the following reasons:  
If we are legally required to disclose information about you and your visits to our sites  
In order to prevent fraud we can also disclose information.  

Third Party Links

Third party links may be found on our site. These third party links have their own privacy policy. By clicking on the link you agree to their privacy policy over which we don’t have any control and we are not responsible for those. 

Cancellation & Refund Policy

 **Cancellation Policy**  
Share-ex believes in serving its customers as good as possible, and therefore comes up with a liberal cancellation policy. Under this policy:   
• Cancellations will be considered only if the request is made within 24 hours of placing an order. However, the cancellation request will not be entertained if the orders have been communicated to the administrator and the process of adding coins to account has been initiated.  
• Share-ex does not accept cancellation requests for points that you are already used.  
• In case you feel that the coins received are not as shown on the website, you must notify our customer service within 24 hours of receiving. The Customer Service team will take an appropriate decision after looking into your complaint.  

Refund Policy

When you buy our packages, your purchase is covered by our 1-day money-back guarantee. If you are, for any reason, not entirely happy with your purchase and/or haven't used all purchased points, we will cheerfully issue a full refund. To request a refund, simply contact us with your purchase details within one (1) day of your purchase. Please include your order number (sent to you via email after ordering) and optionally tell us why you’re requesting a refund – we take customer feedback very seriously and use it to constantly improve our quality of service. Refunds are not being provided for services that you aready have used, because our network fill your account balance (adding points) immediately after purchase done. Refunds are being processed within 7 days period.   
**If in any case, exchanges on your page are reduced after few days, we will not refund your coins and payment. 

Contact Information

For questions, further information, requests or comments please feel free to contact us via support center.
